<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="47">
	<author>LS-Modcompany / kevink98</author>
	
    <version>1.0.1.0</version>
    
	<title>
        <en>GlobalCompanyAddOn - Field Leasing</en>
        <de>GlobalCompanyAddOn - Felder Pachten</de>
        <es>GlobalCompanyAddOn - Alquiler De Campos</es>
        <fr>GlobalCompanyAddOn - Location De Champs.</fr>
        <it>GlobalCompanyAddOn - Noleggio Sul Campi.</it>
    </title>
    
	<description>
        <en><![CDATA[Global CompanyAddOn - Field leasing
        
You don't have enough money for new fields? Then lease them!

For the lease you pay 20% of the regular price of the field once. Then you pay 3% of the regular price of the field every day.
You can find this function in the GlobalCompany menu. There you can also buy or sell a field or end the lease (it's free).

Important information: Leased fields can be sold in the ingame menu. Therefore you should pay attention to what you sell there.

Information: Mod only playable in combination with GlobalCompany!]]></en>		
		<de><![CDATA[Global CompanyAddOn - Felder pachten

Du hast zu wenig Geld für neue Felder? Dann pachte sie doch einfach!

Für die Pacht zahlst du einmalig 20% vom regulären Preis des Feldes. Anschließend zahlst du täglich 3% vom regulären Preis des Feldes.
Die Funktion findest du im GlobalCompany-Menü. Dort kannst du natürlich auch ein Feld kaufen, verkaufen oder die Pacht beenden (ist kostenlos).

Wichtige Information: Gepachtete Felder können im Ingamemenü verkauft werden. Deshalb sollte man drauf achten, was man dort verkauft.

Information: Mod nur in Verbindung mit GlobalCompany spielbar!]]></de>	
 <es><![CDATA[Global CompanyAddOn - Alquiler de campos 
 
 ¿No tienes suficiente dinero para nuevos campos? ¡Entonces alquilalos! Por el contrato de alquiler, usted paga de entrada el 20% del precio normal del campo, y diariamente, usted pagará el 3% del precio del campo.

  Usted puede encontrar esta función en el menú de GlobalCompany. 
  Allí también puede comprar o vender los campos e incluso finalizar contratos de alquiler (sin cargos extra). 
  
  Información importante: Los campos arrendados se pueden vender en el menú del juego. Por lo tanto, debe prestar atención a lo que vende allí.

  Atención: Este mod sólo es jugable en combinación con GlobalCompany.!]]></es>
 
 <it><![CDATA[Global CompanyAddOn - Noleggio sul campo.. Non hanno abbastanza soldi per nuovi campi?  Allora affittateli! Per il contratto di noleggio, si paga l'ingresso 20% del prezzo normale del campo, e ogni giorno, si pagherà il 3% del prezzo del Campo.
 È possibile trovare questa funzione nel menu GlobalCompany. 
 
 Ci si può anche acquistare o vendere i campi e anche fine contratti di noleggio (senza costi aggiuntivi). 
 
 Informazioni importanti: campi leased possono essere venduti nel menu di gioco. Pertanto, si dovrebbe prestare attenzione a ciò che si vende lì.

Attenzione: Questo mod è giocabile solo in combinazione con GlobalCompany.!]]></it>
 
 <fr><![CDATA[Global CompanyAddOn - Acheter, vendre et louer des champs Vous n’avez pas assez d’argent pour de nouveaux champs? Alors louez-les !
 
 Pour le contrat de location, vous payez l’entrée 20% du prix normal du champ, et tous les jours, vous paiez 3% du prix de le Champ. 
 
 Vous pouvez trouver cette fonctionnalité dans le menu GlobalCompany. Ici, vous pouvez également acheter ou vendre les champs et même mettre fin aux contrats de location (pas de frais supplémentaires). 
 
 Informations importantes: les champs loués peuvent être vendus dans le menu du jeu. Par conséquent, vous devriez prêter attention à ce que vous y vendez. 
 
 Attention: Ce mod n’est jouable qu’en combinaison avec GlobalCompany.!]]></fr>		
   </description>
    
	<iconFilename>globalCompanyAddOn_FieldLease.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <globalCompany minimumVersion="1.5.0.0">
        <customClasses>
            <customClass name="GC_AddOnFieldLease"/>
        </customClasses>
    </globalCompany>
		
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/GC_Checker.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/GC_AddOnFieldLease.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>